[ Engine Roaring ]
# # [ Car Radio : Reggae ]
- [ Phone Line Rings ] - [ Man ] Hello ?
It 's dead out here , and I 'm hating you about now .
- What kind of agent are you ? - You 'll find the road .
Kimberly , look , it 's 4 : 00 a.m. In L.A. Can I go back to sleep ?
I was up all night on the red-eye , and it wasn 't first class like you promised .
- Give me credit for the car . Nice ride , huh ? - Yeah , whatever .
By the way , these directions suck . This project sucks .
- K. , it 's a great opportunity . - It 's a reality show pilot .
You sang your way to the top seven the last time you were on TV .
Now you 're the star . You 're Kimberly fucking-Caldwell .
You 're the only celebrity they 've got .
If I 'm such a celebrity , Tommy , get me a movie .
" Kimster , " your Q score 's gonna go way up , and you 'll have a chance to win 90 grand .
- I thought it was a hundred . - Well , I get 10 % , remember ?
Wait . There 's a turnoff .
- # # [ Ends ] - [ Radio Clicks off ]
[ Tommy ] Look , I 've got power yoga in , like , two hours .
- Did you find it yet ? - I don 't know . There 's some old paper mill here .
- But there 's nothin ' about it on the map . - Yeah . That 's gotta be it .
Look , " Kimbo , " you can 't afford to make a wrong turn here . You really don 't have the time .
- Why am I here ? - [ Cell Line Cutting out ] 'Cause this business is tough .
- You 're breaking up . - Of all my clients , you 're the one ...
- Hello ? Hello ? - With the - factor here - [ Line Drops , Beeping ]
Fuck ! [ Screams , Gasps ]
- [ Tires Screeching ] - [ Grunts ]
[ Engine Idling , Stops ]
[ Gasping ]
Oh , my God . Oh , my God . Oh , my God .
Don 't be dead . Don 't be dead .
[ Breathing Deeply ]
[ Door opens , Closes ]
Oh ! [ Gasps ]
Help ! Help !
- [ Cell Phone Beeping ] - Shit !
Anybody !
- [ Groaning ] - Don 't worry . I 'm gonna get you help , okay ?
- [ Coughing ] - No ! No , please ! Please ! No , don 't die !
Come on ! Breathe ! Breathe !
- [ Moaning , Gagging ] - [ Gurgling ]
I 'm here . I 'm here .
- [ Screaming ] - [ Masticating ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Whimpering , Sobbing ]
[ Bones Snapping ]
[ Whimpering , Crying ]
[ Drooling , Chortling ]
- [ Beep ] - [ Thunderclap ]
[ Male Announcer ] It 's the end of the world -
society in chaos , governments no longer in control .
The world has been devastated by a catastrophic disaster , but you 're still alive .
Overnight , you 've been thrust back into the Stone Age .
Modern conveniences are a thing of the past .
Would you have the guts to survive ?
I am retired Marine Colonel Dale Murphy .
Welcome to The Apocalypse .
Over the next five days , these six contestants ... .
will be put to the ultimate test .
I 'm gonna be the ultimate survivor ... .
because on my last show I learned more than anything what it takes to win .
[ Man ] So what 's the tattoo ?
It 's the " infinity " sign , because I wanna be remembered forever .
My friends call me " Jonesy " ... .
but " Fearless " is my middle name .
- Ow ! That sucked , dude . - [ Video Roll Beeps ]
I told you to shave that ride . Can we do that again ?
Hi . I 'm Elena .
I 'm like a fox - sexy , sleek ... .
and I always get what I want .
Nina . I 'm a survivor ... .
because I know there 's only one person I can count on - myself .
I 'm Jake . Three surgeries on my rotator cuff ... .
destroyed my shot at a pro football career -
but not my drive to win .
Amber . One tour of duty in Iraq . They call me " La Conquistadora . "
Enough said . Semper fi .
These six contestants have been thrown together in a devastated wasteland ... .
with only the clothes on their backs ... . and the will to survive .
Rain or shine , in five days , only one will remain .
- Welcome to The Apocalypse . - [ Shell Incoming ]
- [ Switch Clicks ] - Well , what do you think , man ?
We spent all last night cutting it .
- Brando , eat your heart out . - You 're the real deal , Dale .
- That 's why the network loves you . - [ Door opens ]
- It rocks , M. - Damn straight .
- [ Door Closes ] - We 're goin ' to series for sure .
[ Beeping ]
Ah ! Today 's a good day to die . Where 's my producer ?
- It 's brilliant , Michael . Really . - Thank you .
I still don 't see what makes this show any different from that other survivor show .
I don 't watch television .
It 's supposed to take place at the end of the world . That 's what makes it different .
You 're not on some summer resort trying to make alliances .
You 're trying to be the last man standing after the apocalypse .
- It 's killer - Middle America family entertainment , mate . - Booyah .
- That 's damn right . - I 'm so there , dude .
- No . - I plan on being the last woman standing .
[ Scoffs ] Chill , " Ramba . " The prize money 's gonna be mine .
Oh , you two girls could mud wrestle for it .
- Be ratings gold . - Ew .
- You 're stupid , man . - I am tapping ' that .
Hey , it 's the parrot heads . Nice shirts , boys .
Yeah , make fun all you want .
But while you Hollywood freaks are out here sleepin ' on rocks ... .
us parrot heads will be in Margaritaville back at the hotel .
The woods are all wired up - 32 cameras and mikes ready to go .
Oh , you the man , Wojo . Just make sure everything 's copacetic with Neil , okay ?
Yeah . See ya in five days . Enjoy the great outdoors , Tarantino .
- Nice . - [ Laughing ]
I could help you spread it on all those hard-to-reach places .
If I hadn 't seen you eat shit at the X Games last June , maybe you 'd stand a chance .
Hey , I made the street comp finals .
Okay . Here 's a clue . I only give it up to winners -
not guys who choke .
I 'll give you something to choke on .
[ Huffing ]
- [ Engine Starts ] - I wish I had abs like yours .
I do 200 of these a day .
I guess I 'll just stick to my low-carb diet and hope for the best .
- Mara , where the hell 's Kimberly ? - Still no answer .
Goddamn it . I knew that prima donna was a problem when we cast her .
Yeah , but she 's got those Angelina Jolie lips .
You know what I 'm talkin ' about , don 't you ?
- Hello , papa . - It 's gonna be a long five days .
We can 't wait any longer . I gotta shoot , like , now .
You 're the producer , Pop-Tart . That 's why you make the big bucks .
- What are we gonna do ? - Um , well , we can 't recast .
- We 're just gonna have to go with five . - Whoa , whoa . No , wrong .
You know the show II I have to do is shoot your character intro , and we 're good to go .
- No , I don 't think so . - What other choice do we have ?
Um . [ Chuckles ] Okay , yeah . What the hell ?
That 's it ! Show ' em what you 're made of .
All right , boys and girls , listen up !
We have a half-mile hike to the survivalist camp .
Let 's go ! It 's time to move out !
All right . Everybody grab your gear , and let 's get going .
- This is it . - Hey , Michael .
You know I 'm a complete geek without my BlackBerry and my cell .
There 's a good chance I 'll be the first to go .
Come on . Just change your clothes , put on some bug spray .
You 'll be great , even without your " CrackBerry . "
Okay . I 'll do it for you .
- [ Laughing ] - But , um , now , Mara .
It 's M. Now , not Michael .
- Yes , I know . Okay . Sorry . - Right .
God , who am I kidding ?
- [ Door Closes ] - Okay . We 're movin ' out .
You 're all alone out here , so let 's close ranks and stick together .
- # # [ Headphones : Loud Pop ] - Hey , everyone 's leavin ' -
Hello ? Hey . Everyone 's leaving .
- What ? - We 're about to start the game . It 's time to go .
Hi . I 'm Jake . You 're Nina , right ?
Look , I 'm just here for the money , not to make friends , okay ?
Wow . Okay . Fair enough .
- # # [ Continues ] - Oh . Nina . Nina . [ Claps Hands ]
I saw you drop this while you were getting out of the RV .
- Now , M. Said , " No food . " - Oh , well , I 'm vegan .
That might be the only thing I can eat out here .
Well , you can always go chew on a tree . This is cheating .
- Sue me . Give it back . - Uh-uh .
I would have , but ... . since there 's no need to be makin ' friends -
Mmm !
That 's good . [ Chuckles ]
[ Michael ] All right , everybody . Ready ?
And action , Dale .
You cannot survive the apocalypse alone .
So you make friendships , perform tasks together .
You figure out who you need to ride out the chaos and who 's expendable .
Today , we 're gonna split into three teams , go out and search for food .
The number each of you picked decides your teammate .
[ Laughs ] Number one all the way , baby !
[ Chuckles ] You and me , baby . All the way .
- [ Dale ] Who 's got a number 2 ? - I did a number two back at the gas station .
- [ Sighs ] - Come on , dude . That was funny .
[ Mock Gasp ] Oh , sweet .
I guess you and me are a team . Hello ?
All right , boys and girls , it 's the end of the world ...
and the odds are against you from the start .
Radiation poisoning is a reality .
That 's why you 're all wearing these .
Every day , you 'll be given a radiation elimination card .
- And one of them is already contaminated . - [ Device Clicking ]
At the end of the day , the player holding the simulated radiated card is dead .
Don 't worry . It just means you 're disqualified .
But you have a chance to survive the day by giving your card to another player ...
and surviving the radiation elimination .
It 's a test of your personal will , your endurance and fate .
And in The Apocalypse , your fate can change - like that .
Wild animals , bacterial infection and post-apocalyptic crazies ...
are all around you , waiting to take you down .
They 're represented ... . by these .
- We call them " Twists " of Fate . - [ Mouthing Words ]
They are survival challenges , and dozens of them ...
are scattered all over the playing area .
You trigger the motion sensor , and you hear this -
[ Loud , High-pitched Beeping ]
- [ Man Drooling , Chortling ] - [ Beeping Continues ]
Instructions on the back explain your survival challenge .
Accomplish the challenge , and you earn the right ... .
to take your radiated card and give it to any player you choose ... .
and automatically survive the day .
We are going to assemble back here at 1800 hours and see who will perish in the chaos ...
and who is one step closer to $ 100,000 .
Good luck to all of you . Remember -
You have to work as a team to survive the game .
But only one of you can be the ultimate survivalist ... .
after the apocalypse .
- And cut ! Nice work , Dale . [ Grunts ] - All right !
- I 'm ready for my 15 minutes , Hollywood . - [ Scattered Laughter ]
Okay , everybody . [ Coughs ]
[ Beeps ]
Uh , the headsets are transmitting audio and video back to the edit bay , so -
- So don 't take them off . - And , also , uh -
Cell phones and P.D.A. ' s , etcetera - give ' em to Neil .
He 's gonna put them in the RV .
- Have fun . I got to go take a wicked piss , mate . - Mm-hmm .
Okay . I 'm gonna follow Elena and Jake first , as planned .
Uh , just remember , everybody - Let 's make it feel real .
Okay .
- Hey . What 's up ? - I 'm so gonna suck at this .
Why 'd I let you talk me into it ?
Mmm , because I 'm irresistible ?
- You 're a jerk , you know ? - Gotta go .
[ Chuckles , Sniffles ]
Colonel ! W hat happens if we lose the elimination round ?
We go back to the RV . , and you drown your sorrows with me and Jack Daniel 's ... .
- until the game is done . - Oh , that sounds like fun .
But don 't worry , sweetness . I won 't let you lose .
And if any of those pig-fuckin ' hillbillies come around , I got your back .
Hey , bonehead ! I grew up two counties from here !
I never had sex with a pig in my life !
You 're not promoting ' stereotypes , are you , son ?
- [ Silent Stammer ] - Outstanding !
People in these parts might not take that talk too well ! You might wanna put a lid on it !
- Is that all right with you , funnyman ? - Ye-Yes , sir .
Uh - [ Clears Throat ] Th-Th-That 's cool .
You guys got the whole " military bond " thing happenin ' .
- Semper fi and shit . - Yeah .
And we both hate assholes .
Shit . The techies were supposed to finish setting these up before they left .
Put your producer hat away and get your head in the game .
I 'll set these up . I got time to kill anyway .
Thank you . God , I wish I didn 't have to do this .
Old Mikey really put you on the spot , didn 't he ?
I guess he thinks it 'll be entertaining to send a city girl into the woods .
[ Sighs ] Cruel if you ask me , but don 't worry .
There 's something in you he doesn 't see that I do .
You may be pretty , but you 're tougher than you think .
- [ Engine Starts ] - You 'll be all right .
So , " Neen , " which way should we -
I guess we go that way .
[ Beeping ]
[ Zipper Zips ]
[ Grunting , Choking ]
If you eat fish , maybe we should head towards the river to find some food .
I 'm vegan . I don 't eat or use any animal products ... .
including the swimming kind .
Oh . Isn 't your belt made of leather ?
It 's pleather . I 'm not a hypocrite .
No , I didn 't think that you were .
Being vegan is why you got picked to be on the show .
M. Thought there wouldn 't be a lot for you to eat out here ... .
and you might have to resort to gulping down insect larva or something .
[ Sighs ]
It 's the kind of thing America loves in its reality shows , right ?
- America 's sick . - Yeah .
I hate reality shows . They 're pretty idiotic .
- Then why are you doing this ? - Because it 's my job .
It 's M. ' s first project , and I 'm just trying to be supportive .
If I was his girlfriend , I would 've said , " This sucks . You 're on your own . "
- Come on . No , you wouldn 't . - Yeah , I would .
If you haven 't noticed , I can be a bit of a bitch .
Well , if you hate reality shows , then why are you doing this ?
Let 's just keep going . We 've gotta find some food .
[ Beeps ]
[ Camera Whirring ]
[ Rustling In Distance ]
[ Hissing ]
Fucking weekend warriors .
- [ Branch Snaps ] - [ Sharp Thud ]
You 'd better stand down , or someone 's gonna get hurt !
[ Gasping ]
[ Whooping ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Drooling , Chortling ]
Broken arrow . That 's really gonna help us hunt for food .
A spear . I like it . It 's so long and hard .
[ Laughing ] I 'm just goofin ' .
Come on . L - I read your bio back in the R. V.
West Point , 4.0 average . You 're brainy . That 's tight .
I , uh , bet you 're a reader . What 's your favorite book ? Huh ?
I 'm into Cat in the Hat myself .
You did the whole " tour of duty in Iraq " thing . That 's cool .
I 'm more of a pacifist myself , but , hey , I can get down with the patriotism .
- Woman in uniform 's a turn-on . - Will you shut up ?
- Oh . She talks . - Shh !
We 've been hiking for three hours ... .
but we haven 't seen or heard any animals or birds .
It 's dead quiet out here .
It 's freaky , right ? It 's like we 're all alone .
We could get all nasty , and nobody 'd see a thing - except for 30 million people .
Come on . You 're into me , like , a little bit .
You just don 't get it , do you ? I 'm not into men .
[ Gasping ] You-You 're a lesbian ?
How hot is that ?
[ Michael ] All right . Let me just get it focused here .
And action .
So I 'm at the two . I 'm at the one .
I jump . I leap . Bam !
Shoulder was never the same .
Killed my chances at a pro career just like that .
[ Scoffs ] It 's funny .
'Cause you never know when your life 's gonna change .
Man , I wanted to be in the NFL so bad - since I was 6 .
Oh , honey , I totally understand where you 're coming from .
No . Dude , don 't - Don 't look in the lens . Look at -
So , um , then , after college , you just bounced around tryin ' to find yourself ?
Yeah , well , this opportunity came up , you know , to be on this TV show .
I can 't throw a football no more , but I 'm still athletic .
- Mm-hmm . - I figure I 'll use the talents that God gave me , right ?
Well , we 'll have to thank God later .
Yeah , right . Thank God later .
You know , I - I think I hear the river this way . Yeah .
Come on .
God didn 't give you a pair of balls ?
[ Footsteps ]
[ Mara ] How about we take a break ?
We have to find food . If we prove that we 're the best at it ... .
then it 's less likely anybody will give us their radiation card .
[ Sighs ] I haven 't seen anything to eat .
- [ Loud , High-pitched Beeping ] - Ow ! Holy shit !
It 's one of those Twist of Fates . I set it off .
- [ Nina ] Where is it ? - [ Stops ]
" You 've been infected by anthrax from a nearby laboratory explosion .
An antidote can be found by the river . You have two minutes . "
God , I would get this . Yeah , well , good luck . Go .
Hey , come and shoot . We need your footage .
[ Panting ]
- I think I see the river ! - Where ?
- What do you need now ? - That !
[ Female Electronic Voice ] One minute remaining .
Forty-five seconds remaining .
Thirty seconds remaining .
[ Screams , Gasping ]
[ Electronic Voice ] Eight , seven ...
- [ Gasping ] - Six , five ... .
four , three , two - [ Beeps ]
[ Gasping ] Got it .
Yes ! [ Whoops ]
- I can 't believe I did it . - You kicked ass !
[ Out Of Breath ]
Awesome .
All right , guys . One sec . Okay . Keep it loose .
- You ready ? - Go .
Whew . It is hot out here . [ Chuckles ]
You know what ? I think we can fish later .
We are rolling .
[ Sighs , Chuckles ]
I think I need to , uh , cool off .
So ... .
do you want to get , uh , wet ?
- What are you doing ? - M ! What the fuck ?
I am standing here giving it my all , and this jock is just ... standing there !
- Cut ! - Hey , what 's goin ' on , man ?
Look , man , I - I want to create chemistry between you two .
Okay ? You guys are , like , the sex of this thing .
Mm-hmm . You said you wanted a family reality show .
Well , sex is America 's dirty little secret .
Huh ? You can 't talk about it at church , but at home , on TV ... .
people wanna see hard bodies wet and glistening in the sun .
If I do that , I have a mother and six nieces that will never speak to me again .
Look , man , people wanna be entertained .
Elena and I are just greasing the wheels a little .
- Greasin 'the wheels . - Yeah .
Well , look , man , I 'm here to play the game , okay ?
Now you can go grease the wheels .
- You can try catching some fish . - [ Mock Chuckle ]
I 'll see if I can find somethin ' to eat in the woods .
" Grease the wheels . " You two . What - I 'll catch y 'all later .
Catch y 'all later .
Great . I wanted Diddy . I got a Boy Scout .
[ Drooling , Chortling ]
M. , wait . We don 't need Jake .
I 'm all the sex that you want .
- You 're hot , but it 's not the same thing . - Hey , where are you going ?
What , are you gonna go shoot your girlfriend ?
No . Actually , I 've gotta rethink the story lines .
Hey , listen , I 'm doing this gig for , like , free ... .
and I want all the screen time that I can get .
And I know how to make sure that happens .
- Really ? - [ Zipper Unzips ]
Oh .
Works for me .
[ Elena Gulping ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Mara ] You don 't get it .
I 'm , like , a complete spaz when it comes to anything even remotely athletic .
I 'm sorry I didn 't help .
You 're just playing the game . I understand .
I just really need this money .
I 'm not gonna give you my radiation card , if that 's what you 're worried about .
I 'm just thrilled that I actually get to live another day .
[ No Audible Dialogue ]
[ Nina ] Motherfucker .
[ Gasping ]
- [ Shudders ] - Look , I know it hurts ... .
but you don 't need a piece of shit like that in your life .
- You 're better off without him . - [ Crying ]
- I thought he was the one . You know ? - Yeah .
I 've known scumbags like this all my life .
Six months ago , I caught my fiancé in bed with my best friend .
[ Sighs ] Really ?
Top it off -
He used my credit cards to put me into major debt .
That 's why I have to win this game .
The sooner you realize you can only depend on yourself ... .
the better off you 'll be .
Come on .
Take a breath . Let 's go down there and kick his ass .
[ Crying , Laughing ]
- Is that what you did to your fiancé ? - Put him in the hospital .
Come on .
No . I 'll just deal with it in my own way .
It 's what he deserves .
- It 's not me . - Come on .
No . I 'm not like you . I don 't want to be .
- I 'm sorry . That came out wrong . - It 's okay .
- [ Loud Sigh ] - Come on . Just tell me one hot experience that you had .
- Oh , God . - I can get you on Howard Stern if it 's good .
- I got a buddy who works in the studio in New York . - You 're such a moron .
Yeah , but we 're on the same team here . You know , the same ... . Team .
All right . All right , all right . I 'll stop . I 'll stop .
I swear . Cross my heart . No more sex talk .
From now on , you 'll be the uptight lesbian sister I never had . Truce ?
Oh . And now that we 're family , tell me-Who went down on who first ?
- ¡ Pendejo ! - I 'm kidding . I 'm just -
[ Sniffing ]
Is that barbecue ?
Mission fuckin ' - accomplished .
Wait . This is too easy . Maybe this is a trap to make us lose the game .
What trap ? It 's a hunter 's camp , sister .
- What are you doing ? - I 'm starved , and , damn , that smells awesome .
If this is a real hunter 's camp , we can 't just steal his food .
Why the hell not ? It 's a " survival of the fittest " kind of thing . Finders , keepers .
You 're a lesbian . Where are your cojones ?
If we bring this back to share with the others , nobody 's gonna want us out of the game .
- Ow ! - What , it 's hot ?
[ Sighs ]
- Finally , we 're a team . - Don 't push your luck .
Mmm ! Pork .
Man , these hillbillies really know their barbecue .
[ Chopping ]
[ Chopping Stops ]
[ Growls ]
[ Chortling , Growling ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Drooling , Jeering ]
[ Chortling ]
- [ Nina ] So what are you gonna do ? - I 'm getting outta here .
I 'll call the techies to drive me back to Wheeling .
You 're headed the wrong way . RV . And cell phones are back that way .
I can 't get a signal from the RV .
- I 'm just gonna call them from there . - Okay .
Besides , I really don 't want to run into Michael at the trailer .
You 're kidding . No , you 're crazy .
- Okay . - Hello ?
[ Knocking ]
Hello ?
Uh , you can 't just walk into somebody 's house .
I need to use your phone , please .
We shouldn 't be here .
Then just wait for me outside .
I wanna make one phone call , and I 'm gone .
Hello ?
[ Exhales ] Ew .
Oh .
[ Footsteps ] All right . No phone , so -
[ Inhales , Gasps ]
Uh , we done yet ?
[ Gasping ]
Holy shit .
The whole family 's deformed .
God . Look at the twins .
- [ Woman Screaming ] - [ Door opens ]
- [ Screaming Continues ] - [ Man ] You 'll be all right just don 't worry .
Hold on . Don 't drop her .
[ Woman Screaming , Panting ]
Get her over on the table .
[ Muttering ]
There ! Y eah ! Y eah !
Baby 's comin 'now . You stay here with Ma .
I 'll go and fetch some water .
[ Crying , Groaning ]
[ Girl Shushing ]
[ Loud Groaning ]
[ Chittering ]
[ Gasping , Crying ]
[ Chitters ]
[ Shrieks ]
- [ Both Gasping ] - [ Pounding ]
The toolbox !
- [ Pounding Continues ] - Go ! Go !
- It 's locked ! - What do we do now ? - [ Shrieking ]
- Help me ! - [ Pounding Continues ]
[ Shouting ]
[ Both Screaming ]
- [ Gasps ] - [ Flies Buzzing ]
[ Retching ]
There 's light ! There 's light !
[ Gasping ]
- Push ! - [ Grunts ]
- [ Flies Buzzing ] - [ Grunts ]
Uh !
Ma !
[ Panting , Gasping ]
[ Man Grunting ]
[ Gasping , Whimpering ]
[ Screaming , Crying ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Sobbing , Gasping ]
[ Whimpering ] Help me .
- Help me . - [ Grunting ]
[ Object Drops ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Muttering ]
[ Sniffing ]
[ Twig Scrapes ]
[ Vehicle Horn Honks ]
- [ Horn Honking ] - [ Muttering ]
[ Engine Idling ]
[ Muttering ] Fuck .
[ Grunting , Shouting ]
[ Both Arguing ]
[ Gasping ]
- Hey . You good ? - I 'm good .
Can we , uh , keep this as our secret ?
I wouldn 't wanna mess things up with Mara .
- You know , I think she 's the one . - Whatever .
- [ Person Gasping ] - I 'm headin ' back to the RV . You comin ' ?
No . My job 's done .
Just gonna stay here and tan .
Tell Mara I say hi .
- You 're the star . - [ Chuckles ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Gasping , Moaning ]
[ Spits ]
[ Moaning Continues ]
[ Loud Grunt ]
M ? Is that you ?
Don 't screw around . It 's not cool .
- [ Grunts ] - [ Hisses ]
- [ Whimpering ] - [ Grunting ]
- [ Loud , High-pitched Beeping ] - [ Whimpering ]
Aw , shit .
Okay . What 's the challenge ?
- [ Grunts ] - [ Beeping Stops ]
Fuck !
- [ Shrieking ] - No !
- [ Grunting ] - [ Screaming ]
- [ Screaming Stops ] - [ Grunting Continues ]
[ Both Grunting , Gasping ]
[ Barking ]
[ Vehicle Approaching ]
- [ Murmuring ] - [ Man Muttering ]
[ Muttering ]
- [ Truck Door Closes , Engine Starts ] - Mara .
Mara .
[ Drooling , Chortling ]
- [ Grunts ] - [ Groans ]
- [ Bone Snaps ] - [ Whimpering ]
[ Shrieking ]
Hey , Neil . I 'm back , yo . What , you droppin ' a deuce ?
Seriously , Neil , light a match .
- Neil . - [ Computer Beeps ]
Guess you 're not here .
All right . Let 's see what we can see .
Run . No . Run . [ Laughs ]
[ Tapping Button ]
What ?
[ Murmurs ]
Aw , fuck . [ Sighs ]
Let 's see . [ Muttering ]
- Well , this-All right . This works . - [ Footsteps on Gravel ]
Well , what 's the ma - Neil .
I can 't fig-This seems fine .
Great . You know , you spend money on film school just to
[ Door Closes ] - It looks fine .
[ Grunting ]
[ Muttering ] Input , output . Yeah , that works .
- Well , looks good . What is that ? Nina ? - [ Engine Starts ]
[ Grunts ]
Damn it ! Neil , can 't move ! We 're hardwired in !
- [ Growling ] - [ Chortling ]
What the -
[ Grunting , Shouting ]
[ Muttering ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Screaming Continues ]
- This is cool . - It 's good .
- Going for another one , huh ? - Mmm .
The only white meat . If this is what Armageddon 's like , bring it on , baby .
Yeah , maybe next time you should search for a bib .
I 'm so glad I ran into you guys .
Yeah , and don 't forget who got you the nosh , dude .
You win the chance to get rid of that nuclear card , send it someplace else .
No worries .
- Hey , where 's M. And Elena ? - Oh .
Back at the river shooting the unrated version of the DVD .
I 'll see you two later . Oh , dude .
I can 't even move . I 'm so stuffed , sex is gonna have to wait .
[ Farts ] Shit ghost !
- Ow ! - You 're nasty .
If you win , what will you do with the money ?
When I win , I 'm gonna throw the most outrageous beach party in history .
You 're a cliché , dude . How about you ?
Well , when I win , I plan on getting my degree in sports medicine .
Since my arm won 't let me play football anymore , I figure I can still help others .
You know , stay in the game .
Can 't be a football hero , so you 'll settle for a hero of any kind .
Yeah , somethin ' like that .
Nice to know there 's still hope for mankind .
Dude , if you 're sayin ' this to get in her pants , forget about it .
- She doesn 't play on our team . - Shut up . How about you ?
What you plan on doin with the cash ?
I owe my father a bunch of money .
- If I win , I am free and clear of him for good . - Your father ?
He doesn 't approve of my lifestyle .
Wants nothing to do with me .
Hmm . I guess you can 't choose family .
[ Chuckles ] Man , M. Is so screwed .
He wanted a show for Middle America , but he hired a lesbo ... .
a sensitive jock , a bipolar vegan ...
an extreme fuck-up and Miss Hollywood .
Dude , we 're the red-state cast from hell .
- [ All Laughing ] - Oh , God ! Oh , God !
- Yo , Nina . - [ Nina Panting ]
- You all right , Nina ? - [ Groaning ] Mara 's ... . Dead .
- What happened to you ? - We have to get out of here - now .
- What ? - They killed her !
- Hey , look . Calm down . - They 'll find us here !
Take a deep breath . Who will find us here ? What are you talkin ' about ?
These hillbilly freaks ! They killed Mara ... .
and they tied her to the hood of their truck !
We have to get out of here right now !
- This is awesome ! - What is wrong with you ?
- I 'm not kidding ! - Come on . It 's part of the game .
- Post-apocalyptic crazies roaming through the forest . - It 's not a game , okay ?
These hillbillies were eating her finger !
Hillbilly cannibals . M. Is a genius .
- Stop laughing ! - Yo , stop laughing , man , okay ? Hold on .
It 's Mara . She 's M. ' s girlfriend . She was in on it . I got this .
What you saw was special effects .
What I saw was real !
We need to get out of here now !
- Please . - Yeah . Yeah , yeah . We 're going .
This is just a test to see if we bug out .
These kind of shows always screw with their contestants .
You guys wanna go , go ahead . I 'm stayin ' put and winning ' the hundred G 's .
- Then they 'll kill you too , man . - [ Screams ]
- What ? - [ Nina Screams ]
No !
[ Jake ] Nina ? Nina !
- Get the fuck - - That-That 's Kimberly 's tattoo .
Holy shit . That 's her leg .
That 's it . Game 's over . Amber , let 's go .
Come on .
Jonesy !
- They 're fucking cannibals , dude . - Shut up .
- Where the hell 's the RV ? - Just over the ridge .
- Keep quiet and keep moving . - I ain 't stopping ' .
[ Screams ] My foot !
- Let me look at it . - I 'm a shark , man . I gotta keep moving , or I die .
- Shut the fuck up . - You guys get to the R. V.
We 'll be right behind you .
- This is gonna suck . - Oh , shit !
I need to put pressure on that .
- Come on . Give me your wristband . - No !
Look , you don 't have to hide anymore .
How 'd you know ?
When I found out I 'd never play football again , I spiraled down pretty hard .
My therapist told me I should sit in one of her suicide support groups .
You know , give me a better perspective .
There was a girl that used to do the same thing , only she used a bandana .
- So how old is the scar ? - About six months .
What happened ?
I just trusted too many of the wrong people ... . All my life .
- But I 'm past it now . - So it 's old news ?
[ Winces ] Why do you think I came to win this game ?
Guess you 'll get your chance to do just that .
[ Flies Buzzing ]
[ Door Closes ]
You so much as fart , old man , and I 'll drop you .
Don 't kill me , brother . I 'm a good Christian man .
- Shit . Are you sure ? - Yeah . This was the place .
Here are the tire tracks , the empty equipment cases , the garbage .
This is so f ed in the A.
- [ Gasps ] The fucking RV . Is gone ! - Let 's just keep going !
- We 're dead meat . - Where to ? The nearest town is 50 miles away .
We 're all gonna end up hillbilly barbecue .
- I 'm not gonna tell you again . Keep quiet ! - Just come on .
- There 's that old paper mill out by the main road . - It 's abandoned .
- We gotta dig in somewhere . - Maybe there 's a public phone .
Dude , you know why they call it abandoned ? 'Cause there 's nothing in it , including phones !
- Hey ! - Don 't hurt me !
That 's a bear trap . There 's no animals around here .
Why do they have a fucking bear trap set ?
They 're not trapping bears . They 're trapping people .
There 's no wildlife to eat around here . They 're eating us .
Okay , I was wrong . Paper mill 's a great idea . Let 's just get outta here .
No , no , no . Look , man , if we take the road , we 're sitting ducks , all right ?
So I want everyone to stick together and watch where you step .
Yeah , no shit .
Yeah .
[ Groans ]
[ Gasping ]
Who you blowin ' up , old-timer ?
Oh , just the trout .
Only way to bring ' em to the surface .
Dynamite stuns ' em .
Then they float like lily pads , and I just scoop ' em up .
Pretty wife .
Yeah , that 's my Delilah . Gave me the happiest days of my life .
God bless her soul .
You know , you one lucky son of a bitch .
Lotta folk go in them woods . Never seen one come out .
I stay clear of them myself .
How many of those freaks are out there ?
Hard to know . More than the ones you run across . That 's for sure .
What are they ?
Oh , just like you and me , brother , 'cept uglier ... .
and a lot stronger .
Hey , I hit one of them young 'uns once in my pickup .
He popped up and just kept goin ' .
- [ Groans ] - It 's the chemicals changed ' em .
Pulp mill shut down near 30 years ago ...
and left a mess .
And the poison killed off all the game .
Most folks ' round these parts left .
There 's one family that stayed on in this holler ... .
and pretty soon their babies started gushing ' out of their mama 's womb ... .
just as ugly as them trout I got hanging ' out there .
[ Laughs , Mutters ]
And then they grow up , have kids of their own .
Turned out even worse .
You gonna stay for a bite ?
Fish is ugly , but they fry up real good .
No . Much obliged , but I gotta get goin ' .
Well , if you 're gonna head out to get your friends , settle the score ... .
best jump to it before it gets dark .
You don 't wanna be out in them woods at night .
Why do you stay , old-timer ?
Well , I could never leave .
Gotta stay close to my young 'uns .
You motherfucker ! I gonna kill you , man !
[ Shouts ] You killed my boy !
[ Shouting Continues ] I 'm gonna kill you !
I 'll kill you ! I 'll kill you , motherfucker !
I 'll kill you ! [ Groaning ]
[ Shouting , Muffled ] Motherfucker ! I 'm sure ' nough gonna kill you !
I 'll get you ! I 'll teach you to mess with my kids !
Say hello to the missus for me .
[ Rifle Clatters ]
- [ Woman Screaming , Grunting ] - [ Man Grunting ]
[ Screaming , Grunting Continue ]
[ Nina ] It 's one of them .
- It 's Elena . - Yeah ? What makes you think that ?
- [ Grunting ] - [ Screaming ]
Hey !
[ Screaming Continues ]
Get off her !
- Oh , my God . - [ Screaming ]
- Nina , wait ! - [ Grunts ]
- [ Grunting ] - Oh , shit .
[ Whimpers ]
[ Panting ]
[ Screams ]
[ Shrieking ]
[ Jake ] Come on ! Come on !
[ Shrieks ]
- [ Shrieks ] - [ Neck Snaps ] - [ Grunts ]
[ Growling ]
Help me !
[ Whimpering ]
[ Laughing , Sobbing ]
[ Screaming ] Help !
- Where 's Nina ? - She deserted us .
[ Muttering ]
- Son of a bitch ! - Just keep moving .
Look , split up . I 'll find Nina .
- We 'll meet up at the mill . Go ! - Okay .
- Nina ! - [ Nina ] Help me ! Help me !
- Nina ? - Help me !
- [ Jake ] Nina ? - I 'm ... . Down here .
Nina ? Are you okay ?
We gotta get you out of there , all right ?
Look , come on . Come on , Nina .
[ Grunting ] I can 't reach .
- Come on , Nina ! - [ Whimpers ]
Almost .
- [ Grunting ] - Okay , hold on .
- [ Straining ] I 've got you now . I 've got you . - [ Screams ]
- [ Bone Snaps ] - [ Groaning ]
[ Grunting ]
- Try a little right - - [ Grunting ]
[ Grunting , Panting ]
- [ Whimpers , Panting ] - What happened ?
It 's my shoulder . It 's dislocated . You gotta help me pop it in .
Ah , no , Nina ! Easy ! Okay , pull and twist , okay ?
- Go . [ Groaning ] - [ Joint Snapping ]
Help me up . Nina . [ Grunting ]
- It 's like going to war . - [ Grunting ]
- Amber , Jonesy - Did they make it ? - We all made it .
- We 'll meet up with them at the mill , okay ? - [ Vehicle Approaching ]
Let 's go . Let 's go . Let 's go !
Come on , Nina .
[ Gunshot ]
[ Giggling ]
- Let 's go . - Where ?
Shit ! Shit ! Shit !
[ Panting ] You-You totally kicked ass back there .
I 'm serious . You were , like , Xena , Warrior Princess .
You were right . I was a total asshole before .
I 'm never gonna dis you or any other female ever again .
- Great . - It 's cool . We outran ' em .
- [ Twig Snaps ] - Run .
Ow ! Ow !
- Come on . - [ Groaning ]
- Oh , shit . - Come on !
[ Grunts ]
Just-There .
Oh , my God ! [ Screams ]
- Jonesy ! - Help me ! Help me !
Amber ! Amber , help me !
- Jonesy ! - Get me down ! Get me down ! Oh , no ! Oh !
[ Whimpering ] Amber ! Amber , help me !
Christ ! Oh ! Oh , God ! Hurry , Amber !
He 's coming ! He 's com -
- Amber ? Amber , go ! - No !
- Amber , don 't do this ! Get away ! - I 'm not leaving you !
Go ! Run ! No ! Amber , no !
Oh , God ! Oh , God !
- [ Gasps ] - Amber ?
- [ Gasping ] - Jonesy !
[ Groaning ]
- [ Laughing ] - Jonesy !
Give me your hand !
[ Grunting , Laughing ]
[ Mutters ]
[ Laughing ]
- Huh ? - [ Mutters ]
[ Amber ] Don 't look down .
[ Jonesy Whimpering ]
I 'm here .
Amber , I 'm scared .
[ Amber ] You 're not alone .
All right . I 'm gonna get us out of here .
[ Gasps ] You know , my mother always used to say I 'd live forev -
[ Laughing , Slurping ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Shouts ]
- There it is . - Jonesy wasn 't kidding . - [ Drooling , Chortling ]
This place is dead .
" Birth defects . " No shit .
Can 't see anything . How the hell are we gonna find ' em in here ?
Let Amber and Jonesy find us .
- Where 'd you get that ? - I brought it with me for the game .
- I thought it might come in handy . - That 's cheating .
Sue me .
You think they 're up there ? Maybe they found a C.B. Radio , called for help .
I guess I 'll go first .
Be careful .
- They gotta be around here somewhere . - [ Picks Up Phone ]
If they even made it here at all .
Come on , guys . Where you at ?
[ Screams ] Oh , my God .
- She was just a little girl . - Looks like she 's been in there forever .
- She 's hiding . - Yeah , but from whom ?
- This isn 't right . - [ Vehicle Approaching ]
- Nina , no ! Nina ! No , Nina ! - [ Shouts ]
- Too late ! We 've gotta get out of here now ! - No ! No , Nina !
We cannot leave them , okay ? Let 's go .
Look , there 's the RV . I don 't see ' em .
Oh , Jesus . This family 's been doing this for decades .
[ Man Screaming ]
Oh , my God ! That sounds like M. Screaming .
Okay , I 'm going down there .
[ Screaming Continues ]
No , no , no , no . Hold this .
- [ Screaming Continues ] - Shit . You got my back ?
[ Grunts ]
- [ Michael ] Somebody ! Please ! - M ? M ?
Come on . Come on . Come on ! Fuck !
- Fuck face ! - M !
Get me the fuck out of here !
- Fuck ! Get me the fuck - - [ Giggles ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Muffled Screaming ]
[ Michael Continues Shouting ]
- M ? - Get me the fuck out !
Help me , please ! God , help ! Please don 't !
- M ? - Please !
[ Screaming ]
[ Choking , Gurgling ]
Oh ! M ! Nina , it 's a trap !
[ Neck Snapping ]
[ Grunts ] Oh , shit !
Shit .
[ Grunts ]
- [ Loud Pounding ] - # # [ Woman Humming ]
[ Man on TV ] Do you have moral rottenness ?
[ TVContinues , Indistinct ]
Brothers and sisters , you must know ...
that we live in a world of technology .
- [ TVContinues , Indistinct ] - [ Gasps ]
[ Man on TVContinues ] ... engaging in extracurricular sexuality ...
homosexuality .
[ TVContinues , Indistinct ]
No ! [ Screams ]
Will it be heaven or hell that you decide on ?
- This is the crossroad - - [ Flies Buzzing ]
- Do you take the turn for heaven ... - [ Whimpering ]
Or do you take the wrong turn to hell ?
- [ TVContinues , Indistinct ] - [ Mutters ]
[ Grunts ]
It 's what you need to find your way .
- [ Mutters ] - It 's what you need to find that light .
Stay away from the darkness . Do not take a wrong turn -
... to living a life of sin , of personal destruction -
[ Gasps ]
Here I have the book that will save your life -
[ TVContinues , Indistinct ]
- [ Grunting ] - [ Gasps ]
- [ Rattling Cage ] - [ Grunting ]
Living a life of sin will only lead
[ Hammer Clicks ] - [ Gasps ]
[ Laughing ]
Fuck you !
[ Grunts ]
[ Jake ] Don 't do it ! Leave her alone !
[ Flies Buzzing ]
[ Nina Groaning ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Screaming ]
Leave her alone ! Leave her alone !
[ Screams , Gasps ]
[ Coughing ]
- Stop messing with her ! - [ Mutters ]
[ Whimpering ]
Stop it .
[ Mutters ]
[ Whimpering , Coughing ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Muttering Prayer ]
What the fuck is wrong with you people ?
Amen .
[ Groaning ]
[ Gasping ] I hope you fucking choke !
- [ Screaming ] - Leave her alone !
[ Shouting , Pounding Table ]
[ Coughing ]
[ Coughing Continues ]
[ Footsteps ]
[ Loud Whirring ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Footsteps ]
Please ! Let us go !
[ Groans , Coughs ]
- Come on , man . Help ! - Help .
- Help . Help . - Help .
[ Mocking Continues ]
- [ Jake ] Come on . Let us go ! - [ Mocking ] Let us go !
- Let us go ! Nina ! [ Pleading , Indistinct ] - [ Laughter ]
[ Man Grunting ]
[ Device Clicking ]
- Help ! Help ! - [ Clicking Continues ]
[ Jake ] Help ! Please ! We 're in here ! We 're trapped !
Please , someone , help us ! Help us !
Fuck !
- [ Clicking Continues ] - [ Jake ] Please help us ! We 're in here !
- [ Mutters ] - Damn it ! Don 't leave !
- [ Whimpering ] Help us ! Please help us ! - [ Clicking Continues ]
Please help us ! Please help us !
[ Groans ]
[ Object Clatters ]
- [ Grunts ] - This way .
[ Screaming ]
[ Shouts ]
Ooh-rah .
[ Beeps ]
[ Gasps ] Nina ! Nina !
Nina ! Come on . Wake up .
Nina , wake up ! Nina !
Can you pull your hands free ?
I need you to pull your hands free .
[ Groaning ]
I can 't .
Nina , you 've gotta try ! Nina !
- Nina , wake up ! Nina ! - Shh .
- Dale ? - [ Whispers ] Be quiet .
I gotta do this . Breathe through it .
Ready ? Okay ? Go .
- [ Screams ] - Shh . Shh .
One more .
Go .
[ Screams ]
Get up .
- [ Groans ] - There 's an exit door through there .
We are right behind you .
Go !
Dale .
[ Gasping , Whimpering ]
[ Gasps ]
I want you to go find Nina . [ Grunts ]
- Dale ! - Hey ! Hey !
Find Nina . Go . I 've got it . Go !
[ Grunts ]
Is that all you got , bitch ?
- [ Growling ] - [ Grunting ]
[ Grunting , Choking ]
[ Grunting Continues ]
Fuck you ! [ Choking ]
[ Sobbing ]
[ Screaming ] No ! No !
[ Coughing ]
[ Wheezing , Screams ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Screams , Grunts ]
[ Screams ]
Let go of me , you son of a bitch ! Let go of me !
[ Grunting ]
[ Jake ] Let go ! Let go of me !
- Let go of me ! - [ Screaming ] Shit !
Let go of me , you son of a bitch !
- [ Shrieking ] - No ! No !
[ Shouting ]
[ Screams ]
No ! [ Grunting ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Groaning , Grunts ]
[ Grunting Continues ]
[ Shouting ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Grunts ] Come on !
[ Shouting , Grunts ]
[ Both Screaming ]
[ Muck Sloshing ]
You know you didn 't have to come back for me , right ?
Sue me .
Wow .
Nice ride .
You wanna take it for a spin ?
[ Sniffles ] Why not ? It 's the least this fucked-up family owes us .
[ Engine Starts ]
[ Clattering ]
Mmm . Mmm .
[ Cooing ]
[ Muttering ]
[ Crying ]
[ Man Cackling ]